Being an information technology, or IT, worker is not a job I envy.
做信息技术（即IT）工作者，这份工作我并不羡慕。
IT workers are the ones who, right in the middle of a critical meeting, are expected to instantly fix the projector that’s no longer working.
关键会议正开到一半，投影仪却不工作了，这时大家指望立刻把它修好的，就是IT工作者。
They have to tolerate the bad tempers of colleagues frustrated at the number of times they’ve had to call the help desk for the same issue.
他们不得不忍受同事的坏脾气：同事们为同一个问题只好一遍遍给服务台打电话，正为此恼火不已。
They are also the ones who know there are systems that are more powerful, more reliable and faster, but their employer simply will not put up the funds to buy them.
也正是他们知道，有些系统更强大、更可靠、速度更快，可雇主就是不肯拿出资金来购买。
According to a recent survey, employees who have a job reliant on IT support consider IT a major source of job dissatisfaction.
根据最近的一项调查，工作依赖IT支持的员工认为，IT是他们对工作不满的一大根源。
Through no fault of their own, they can suddenly find their productivity deteriorating or quality control non-existent.
明明不是他们自己的过错，他们却可能突然发现工作效率不断下滑，或者质量控制荡然无存。
And there’s little they can do about it.
而对此，他们几乎无能为力。
The experience of using IT penetrates almost the entire work field.
使用IT的体验几乎渗透到了整个工作领域。
It has become a crucial part of employees’ overall work experience.
它已经成为员工整体工作体验中至关重要的一部分。
When IT is operating as it should, employee self-confidence swells.
IT正常运转的时候，员工的自信心就会高涨。
Their job satisfaction, too, can surge when well-functioning machines relieve them of dull tasks or repetitive processes.
运转良好的机器让员工摆脱枯燥的任务或重复的流程时，他们的工作满意度也可能飙升。
But if there’s one thing that triggers widespread employee frustration, it’s an IT transformation project gone wrong, where swollen expectations have been popped and a long list of promised efficiencies has been reversed.
但如果说有哪件事会引发员工普遍的挫败感，那就是出了差错的IT改造项目：膨胀的期望被戳破，原先承诺的一长串效率提升非但没有兑现，反而成了效率倒退。
This occurs when business leaders implement IT initiatives with little consideration of how those changes will impact the end user.
企业领导者在推行IT新举措时，如果几乎不考虑这些变化会给终端用户带来什么影响，就会出现这种情况。
Which is why managers should appreciate just how influential the IT user experience is to their employees, and exert substantial effort in ensuring their IT team eliminates programming errors and application crashes.
正因如此，管理者应该充分认识到IT用户体验对员工的影响究竟有多大，并投入大量精力，确保自己的IT团队消除编程错误和应用程序崩溃。
Adequate and timely IT support should also be available to enable users to cope with technological issues at work.
还应该提供充分、及时的IT支持，使用户能够应对工作中的技术问题。
More importantly, IT practitioners need to understand what employees experience mentally when they use IT.
更重要的是，IT从业者需要了解员工在使用IT时有怎样的心理感受。
Therefore, businesses need to set up their IT infrastructure so that it is designed to fit in with their employees’ work, rather than adjust their work to fit in with the company’s IT limitations.
因此，企业需要搭建好自己的IT基础设施，使其在设计上适应员工的工作，而不是调整员工的工作去适应公司IT的局限。